		 ~~         L@mBerT       ~~
		-------------------------------------		
		One Piece Episode List
		-------------------------------------

Season 1 : First Voyage
==================

01 	"I'm Gonna Be King of the Pirates!"
02 	"Roronoa Zolo: Pirate Hunter"
03 	"An Unlikely Pair: The Pirate & The Pirate Hunter"
04 	"The Passing Of The Hat"
05 	"The Circus Comes To Town" 
06 	"The Beast Breaker"
07 	"The Desperate Duel"
08 	"Who Gets the Last Laugh?"
09 	"The Teller of Tales"
10	"The Weirdest Guy Ever! Jango the Hypnotist!"
11 	"Expose the Plot! Pirate Butler, Captain Kuro!"
12 	"Clash with the Black Cat Pirates! The Great Battle on the Slope!"
13 	"The Black Cat Pirates"
14	"Luffy Back in Action! Miss Kaya's Desperate Resistance!"	
15	"Beat Kuro! Usopp the Man's Tearful Resolve!"
16	"Protect Kaya! The Usopp Pirates' Great Efforts!"
17	"Angry Explosion! Kuro vs. Luffy! How it Ends!"
18	"You're the Weird Creature! Gaimon and His Strange Friends!"
19	"The Three-Sword Style's Past! Zoro and Kuina's Vow!"
20	"Famous Cook! Sanji of the Sea Restaurant!"
21	"Unwelcome Customer! Sanji's Food and Ghin's Debt!"
22	"The Strongest Pirate Fleet! Commodore Don Krieg!"
23	"Protect Baratie! The Great Pirate, Red Foot Zeff!"
24	"Hawk-Eye Mihawk! The Great Swordsman Zoro Falls At Sea!"
25	"The Deadly Foot Technique Bursts Forth! Sanji vs. The Invincible Pearl!"
26	"Zeff and Sanji's Dream! The Illusory All Blue!"
27	"Cool-headed, Cold-hearted Demon! Pirate Fleet Chief Commander Ghin!"
28	"I Won't Die! Fierce Battle, Luffy vs. Krieg!"
29	"The Conclusion of the Deadly Battle! A Spear of Blind Determination!"
30	"Set Sail! The Seafaring Cook Sets off With Luffy!"
31	"The Worst Man in the Eastern Seas! Fishman Pirate Arlong!"
32	"Witch of Cocoyashi Village! Arlong's Female Leader!"
33	"Usopp Dead?! When is Luffy Going to Make Landfall?!
34	"Everyone's Gathered! Usopp Speaks the Truth About Nami!"
35	"Untold Past! Female Warrior Bellemere!"
36	"Survive! Mother Bellemere and Nami's Bond!"
37	"Luffy Rises! Result of the Broken Promise!"
38	"Luffy in Big Trouble! Fishmen vs. the Luffy Pirates!"
39	"Luffy Submerged! Zoro vs. Hatchan the Octopus!"
40	"Proud Warriors! Sanji and Usopp's Fierce Battles!"
41	"Luffy at Full Power! Nami's Determination and the Straw Hat!"
42	"Explosion! Fishman Arlong's Fierce Assasult From the Sea!"
43	"End of the Fishman Empire! Nami's My Friend!"
44	"Setting Out with a Smile! Farewell, Hometown Cocoyashi Village!"
45	"Bounty! Straw Hat Luffy Becomes Known to the World!"
46	"Chase Straw Hat! Little Buggy's Big Adventure!"
47	"The Wait is Over! The Return of Captain Buggy!"
48	"The Town of the Beginning and the End! Landfall at Logue Town!"
49	"Kitetsu III and Yubashiri! Zoro’s New Swords and the Woman Sergeant Major!"
50	"Usopp vs. Daddy the Parent! Showdown at High!"
51	"Fiery Cooking Battle? Sanji vs. the Beautiful Chef!"
52	"Buggy's Revenge! The Man Who Smiles On the Execution Platform!"
53	"The Legend Has Started! Head for the Grand Line!"
54	"Precursor to a New Adventure! Apis, a Mysterious Girl!"
55	"Miraculous Creature! Apis' Secret and the Legendary Island!"
56	"Eric Attacks! Great Escape from Warship Island!"
57	"A Solitary Island in the Distant Sea! The Legendary Lost Island!"
58	"Showdown in the Ruins! Tense Zoro vs. Eric!"
59	"Luffy, Completely Surrounded! Commodore Nelson's Secret Strategy!"
60	"Through the Sky They Soar! The 1000 Year Legend Lives Again!"
61 	"An Angry Showdown! Cross the Red Line!"
62	"The First Line of Defense? The Giant Whale Laboon Appears!"


^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^

	~~	Thank You for Downloading  !!       ~~

To download more of my Torrents ,, or if U have some request (specially in anime)..then PM me here
__________________________________________________________
	http://kickass.to/user/LamBerT_vin/
	https://thepiratebay.se/user/LamBerT_vin
	http://1337x.org/user/LamBerT/
__________________________________________________________

<<  Please SEED.... These Torrents would DIE without YOUR support  >>

		Cheers !!  ^_^

		HAPPY SEEDING !!
^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^